Hi, and welcome to A/B testing.
大家好 欢迎来到 A/B 测试
In this course, we'll discuss how to run experiments, or A/B tests for businesses
本课中 我们将讨论如何为建有网站或移动应用的企业
who have an online presence via websites or mobile apps, for example.
运行试验或 A/B 测试
>> A/B tests allow you to determine scientifically how to optimize a website
A/B 测试可以通过尝试可能的改变
or a mobile app by trying out possible changes and
寻找用户更喜欢的方式
seeing what performs better with your users.
帮助你科学地确定如何优化网站或移动应用
Using A/B tests means that you can get data to make decisions
使用 A/B 测试意味着你可以根据数据做出决定
rather than relying on intuition or hippos ie,
而不是依赖猜想或臆测 例如
the highest paid person's opinion >> In this course,
— 薪酬最高人员的意见 — 在本课程中
we'll be going over the process form start to finish.
我们将从头到尾地了解这个过程
Everything from deciding what change you want to test in the first place,
从一开始确定你要测试的变更
through drawing a conclusion.
到得出结论的整个过程
>> On the other hand, we won't focus on how to implement
另一方面 我们不会关注如何实施
your using A/B testing framework >> This
你的A/B 测试框架
course is about how to design a task, choose metrics, and analyze the results.
本课程会讲授如何设计任务、选择指标并分析结果
>> Sounds good.
听起来十分不错
But, before we jump into that, why don't we take a minute to introduce ourselves?
但是 在我们开始之前 我们何不花点时间介绍一下我们自己？
>> Sure. I'm Diane Tang.
好的 我是Diane Tang
I have a PhD in computer science and I worked for over 12 years at Google.
计算机博士 在 Google 工作了 12 年多
I worked on just about every aspect of experimentation.
我的工作涉及实验的各个方面
Review from the underlying infrastructure to designing metrics and
审查潜在的基础架构、设计指标和 dashboard
dashboards to running and analyzing experiments to the processing culture,
运行分析实验 以及
needed to facilitate data driven decisions.
用以推动数据驱动决策的处理环境
I'll be giving you the practical engineering perspective
我会从实践工程的角度
on how to design and analyze experiments for a bus decision making.
讲述如何设计与分析总线决策制定的实验
>> My name is Carrie Grimes Bostock, I have a PhD in statistics, and
我叫Carrie Grimes Bostock 统计学博士
I've worked at Google for almost 12 years, in all kinds of different areas.
在 Google 工作近12年 涉及各种不同领域
I'll be giving you the more statistical perspective on how you draw
在如何得出 A/B 试验的结论方面
conclusions in A/B experiments.
我将给大家提出统计学方面的意见
And I'm Caroline Buckey.
我是 Caroline Buckey
I'm, of course, a developer at UDacity and before that,
优达学城的开发人员 在此之前
I was a software engineer in Silicon Valley.
我是硅谷的软件工程师
I'll be going over examples, diving into details and making sure you
我将通过各种示例 研究所有细节并确保
have everything you need to apply what you're learning on your own
你能够将自学的内容运用于实践